http://www.tourspecgolf.com/privacy-policy/

zestaim
Golf ClubsDriversNon-Conforming / HI CORDriversUSGA Conforming & HI-COR Drivers from Japan
Japan is known for their high quality golf drivers made of the the best materials and tested to improve distance and accuracy.  Choose the Non-Conforming option to see all HI COR drivers.View moreFairway WoodsFairway WoodsFairway Woods from Japan
We sell ALL Japanese fairway woods.  If you do not see what you are looking for, please ask!View moreUtility / HybridsUtility / HybridsUtility Woods & Hybrids
We sell ALL Japanese Utility / Hybrids.  If you do not see what you want, please ask!View moreIron SetsIron SetsIron Sets from Japan
Made in Japan iron sets are known for their soft feel at impact.  Japanese forged irons are offered here at Tour Spec Golf with many custom options and specs to choose from. View moreWedgesWedgesWedges from Japan
Feel the difference of Japan Forged wedges at impact and notice the spin of your approach to the green.   We offer USGA legal wedges or choose HIGH SPIN illegal grooves.View morePuttersPuttersRare & Luxury Putters
The most rare, limited, and sought out putters are available to order here.  See what defines quality in a high-end putter.View moreHead OnlyDriver HeadsFairway Wood HeadsUtility / Hybrid HeadsIron HeadsWedge HeadsPutter HeadsGolf PartsHead OnlyHead Only Golf Components from Japan
Look through our high quality HEAD ONLY options.  Buy the heads only OR ask us to do a TSG Club Works custom installation for free with the purchase of Head, Shaft, and Grip.View moreFull SetsFull SetsFull Golf Sets from JapanView moreShafts / GripsGraphite ShaftsDriver ShaftsFairway Wood ShaftsUtility / Hybrid ShaftsIron ShaftsWedge ShaftsPutter ShaftsGraphite ShaftsGraphite Shafts
Japanese shafts are made of the best quality material. Some produce higher ball flights for those wanting distance, while other keep the ball low for those looking for more roll. View moreSteel ShaftsDriver / Fairway Wood ShaftsUtility / Hybrids ShaftsIron ShaftsWedge ShaftsPutter ShaftsSteel ShaftsSteel Shafts
Japanese shafts are made of the best quality material. Some produce higher ball flights for those wanting distance, while other keep the ball low for those looking for more roll. View moreGripsGripsGrips
Japanese grips are made of the best quality material.View moreGolf BagsCaddy BagsCaddy BagsFREE Shipping for all Caddy & Stand Bags!
Impress on the Golf course with a beautiful Japan only golf bag. Many of our customers say they receive more compliments on their Japanese golf bag and clubs than their luxury car!
View moreStand BagsStand BagsFREE Shipping for all Caddy & Stand Bags!
Impress on the Golf course with a beautiful Japan only golf bag. Many of our customers say they receive more compliments on their Japanese golf bag and clubs than their luxury car! View moreOther BagsOther BagsOther Bags from Japan
Impress on the Golf course with a beautiful Japan only golf bag. Many of our customers say they receive more compliments on their Japanese golf bag and clubs than their luxury car! View moreAccessoriesGolf BallsGolf BallsGolf Balls from Japan
Try Japanese golf balls packed with technology due to their larger budget for research, testing and development. View moreHead coversHead coversHead Covers
Add a nice finishing touch to complete your set and protect your golf clubs with some cool head coversView moreGlovesGlovesGloves from JapanView moreMarkersMarkersBall MarkersView moreOther AccessoriesOther AccessoriesOther AccessoriesView moreApparelGolf caps & visorsGolf caps & visorsGolf Caps & VisorsView moreShoesShoesGolf ShoesView moreWomensDriversWomens DriversWomen's Drivers from JapanView moreFairway WoodsWomens Fairway WoodsWomen's Fairway woodsView moreUtility / HybridsWomens Utility / HybridsWomen's Hybrids & Utility woodsView moreIronsWomens IronsWomen's Iron SetsView moreWedgesWomens WedgesWomen's WedgesView morePuttersWomens PuttersWomen's PuttersView moreLeft HandedDrivers Left Handed Drivers Left Handed DriversView moreFairway WoodsLeft Handed Fairway WoodsLeft Handed Fairway WoodsView moreUtility / HybridsLeft Handed Utility / HybridsLeft Handed Hybrids & Utility WoodsView moreIronsLeft Handed IronsLeft Handed Iron SetsView moreWedgesLeft Handed WedgesLeft Handed WedgesView morePuttersLeft Handed PuttersLeft Handed PuttersView moreSale
Blog
Contact Us
Shopping Cart
Account DashboardMy OrdersMy Wish ListAddress BookAccount InformationMy Product ReviewsNewsletter Subscriptions
My Rewards
Privacy settingsLogout
Settings
Currency
USD
USD - US Dollar
SGD - Singapore Dollar
KRW - South Korean Won
Password
Forgot Your Password?
Don't Have An Account? Sign-Up
LOGIN
Or login with a social account
Sign in with Facebook
Sign in with Google
Create An Account
Back
Password
State/Province
Please select a state.
Zip/Postal Code
Country
United KingdomUnited States AustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelgiumBelizeBermudaBrazilBruneiBulgariaCambodiaCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsChileChinaColombiaCosta RicaCôte d’IvoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzechiaDenmarkDominican RepublicEgyptEstoniaFijiFinlandFranceGermanyGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuamHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaLaosLuxembourgMacau SAR ChinaMalaysiaMaltaMexicoMonacoMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMyanmar (Burma)NepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPanamaPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSouth AfricaSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSt. LuciaSwedenSwitzerlandTaiwanThailandTurkeyUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUzbekistanVatican CityVietnam
Register
Forgot Password
Please enter your email address below to receive a password reset link.
Email
Please type the letters below
Submit
Go back
This privacy policy sets out how Tourspecgolf uses and protects any information that you give Tourspecgolf when you use this website. Tourspecgolf is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Tourspecgolf may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
We may use the information for remarketing to advertise online.
We may use the information to show our ads on sites across the Internet.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Google may use these cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [email protected]
You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ad Settings.  Alternatively, you may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
You may opt out of our site internal cookie privacy solution by opening the popup in the bottom left side of the page, that will trigger the cookie consent popup again allowing you to opt out.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists essential cookies that we collect for our website to function properly. Without these cookies, you will not be able to perform core site functions such as logging in, or purchasing products.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Managing cookies on your device
Cookies are perfectly safe to be stored on your computer and almost all web browsers have cookie storage enabled as a default setting. However, all browsers have the option to disable cookie storage on your computer if you wish to do this. Please be aware disabling cookies will limit the functionality we can offer at the our website. To find out more about setting your cookie preferences visit the website appropriate to your own browser.
